<subtitle>
    <objective>Damage Pixy's aircraft.</objective>
    
    <!-- Phase 1 -->
    <A1_1>Confirmed reactivation of nuclear silo! Galm Team, continue your mission. Engage!</A1_1>
    <A1_2>Stand by. We're analyzing the situation.</A1_2>
    <P1_1>Here comes the snow...</P1_1>
    <A1_3>Shoot down the enemy. I'll run a plane analysis and fill you in ASAP!</A1_3>
    <P1_2>Those who survive a long time on the battlefield start to think they're invincible.</P1_2>
    <P1_3>I bet you do, too, Buddy.</P1_3>
    
    <!-- Phase 2 -->
    <A2_1>Phase 1 analysis complete!</A2_1>
    <A2_2>Transmission from enemy craft detected. He's controlling the V2 launch!</A2_2>
    <P2_1>Can you see any borders from here? What has borders given us?</P2_1>
    <P2_2>We're going to start over from scratch. That's what V2 is for.</P2_2>

    <!-- Phase 2 Script : Depends on Ace Style -->
    <P2_S1>It's pretty ironic, Buddy. A couple of dogs like us fightin' the last battle.</P2_S1>
    <P2_S2>It's not over, Buddy. This is where it all starts. You know what I'm talkin' about, right?</P2_S2>
    <P2_S3>There's only one way, Buddy. You've gotta fight for what you believe in.</P2_S3>

    <!-- Phase 2 Script : Random -->
    <P2_3>There's no mercy in war. People live and people die. That's all there is to it.</P2_3>
    <P2_4>You fired up? Come shoot me down.</P2_4>
    
    <P3_0>It's time.</P3_0>

    <!-- Cutscene -->
    <AC_1>Dammit! Confirmed launch of V2!</AC_1>
    <PC_2>Too bad, Buddy. </PC_2>
    <PC_3>This twisted game needs to be reset. </PC_3>
    <PC_4>We'll start over from "zero" with this V2 and entrust the future to the next generation.</PC_4>
    <AC_5>This is AWACS. Listen up, Galm 1!</AC_5>
    <AC_6>We've completed analysis of the enemy craft.</AC_6>
    <AC_7>Codename: Morgan.</AC_7>
    <AC_8>This plane is protected by an ECM defense system.</AC_8>
    <AC_9>Its only weak point is in the front air intake.</AC_9>
    <AC_10>You'll have to attack it head-on.</AC_10>
    <AC_11>Go! Take down Morgan!</AC_11>
    <AC_12>You're the only one who can stop him.</AC_12>
    <AC_13>Demon Lord of the Round Table... I pray for your success!</AC_13>
    
    <!-- Phase 3 -->
    <P3_1>You and I are opposite sides of the same coin.</P3_1>
    <P3_2>When we face each other, we can finally see our true selves.</P3_2>
    <P3_3>There may be a resemblance, but we never face the same direction.</P3_3>

    <!-- Time / Low HP -->
    <A3_1>Galm 1, go for his front air intake!</A3_1>
    <P3_5>Fire away, coward!</P3_5>
    <P3_6>Come on!</P3_6>

    <!-- Phase 3 Remained time alert -->
    <!-- 5 -->
    <A3_T5>V2 reentry in 5 minutes.</A3_T5>
    <P3_T5>Try again from head on.</P3_T5>

    <!-- 4 -->
    <A3_T4>V2 reentry in 4 minutes.</A3_T4>
    <P3_T4>Now we find out who's number one.</P3_T4>

    <!-- 3 -->
    <A3_T3>V2 reentry in 3 minutes.</A3_T3>
    <P3_T3>Looks like we've both still got what it takes.</P3_T3>
    
    <!-- 2.5-->
    <A3_T2.5>Fire away at him from head on!</A3_T2.5>
    <P3_T2.5>Come on.</P3_T2.5>
    
    <!-- 2 -->
    <A3_T2>2 minutes left.</A3_T2>
    
    <!-- 1 -->
    <A3_T1>1 minute left!</A3_T1>
    <P3_T1>Get ready!</P3_T1>
    
    <!-- Mission Failed -->
    <A1_X>Operation failed. Return to base!</A1_X>
    <A3_X>The V2 re-entry has started! You're too late.</A3_X>

    <!-- Ending Cutscene -->
    <AE_1>Mission accomplished, Cipher.</AE_1>
    <AE_2>Come on, let's go back home.</AE_2>
    <AE_3>We wouldn't want to keep anyone waiting for you.</AE_3>
    
    <!-- Dead -->
    <AX_1>Galm 1 is hit!</AX_1>
    <AX_2>Galm 1 is going down!</AX_2>
    <AX_3>Galm 1 is down!</AX_3>
</subtitle>